

# Sina Kheiri

# Front-End Developer | Next.js/React.js | Web3

As a **Front-end developer** with **4 years of experience**, I possess a **diverse skill set** in my field of work. With a strong focus on delivering **clean code**, **high-quality projects** and **exceptional user interfaces**, I am committed to staying **up-to-date** with the latest industry trends and best practices.

I also have the knowledge and skills for UI Design and I have created **User personas, Wireframes, High fidelity projects** and **Prototypes** using **Figma and Adobe XD**.

sinakheiri.dev@gmail.com

**\** +989100056440

Karaj, Alborz, Iran

sinakheiri.dev

github.com/IWarwolfl

in linkedin.com/in/sinakheiri-dev

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Senior Front-end Developer

Remote in Exmodules (<u>twitter</u>) 2023 – 2024

- **Led a team** of developers and provided guidance on project requirements.
- Created seamless user interfaces for various projects (+10).
- Learned and improved skills in Next.js,
   TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS.
- Delved into Web3 world and worked with
   MetaMask and Smart Contracts to develop crypto based websites.

## Front-end Developer

Full-time in Agahpadidar (<u>linkedin</u>) 2021 – 2023

- Established connections to Restful APIs using Async Thunks and Axios.
- Utilized Redux toolit for state management.
- Participated in Agile development
   methodologies such as daily stand-ups and sprint planning.

#### **SKILLS**

# - Programming languages

Javascript, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS

#### - Frameworks

Next.js, Material UI, Tailwind CSS

#### State Management

Zustand, Redux toolkit

#### Testing

Jest

#### - Libraries

Web3, GSAP, Lenis, TanStack Query, React hook form, zod, React.js, Swiper, Axios, Formik, Yup, Recharts.js, Jquery

#### - UI Design

Figma, Adobe XD, Responsive Web Design, Adobe Illustrator

#### Other

shadcn/ui, Git, Github, Agile Methodoligies, Clean Code Principles

#### Frontend Developer and UI Designer

Freelance in ponisha(link)

2018 - 2021

- Designed **User interfaces** for mobile apps and websites.
- Created **User personas**, **Wireframes**, **High fidelity designs**, and integrated **Prototyping**.
- Developed static web pages and HTML templates.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Islamic Azad University Of Karaj

Bachelor Degree, Computer Software Engineering

2022 - present

#### **Shahid Beheshti University**

Associate degree, Biomedical Engineering 2019 – 2022

#### **LANGUAGES**

Persian(mother tongue)
English(Advanced)

# **PROJECTS** [viewable by attached links and code is available in my github]

## - BlockT[Front-end Development(Next.js - Web3)]

BlockT is a seamless **Dapp** that utilizes **Web3**, connects to **Smart contracts** and sends transactions on Polygon Mumbai testnet.

#### -<u>Farzam.at</u>[Front-end Development(Next.js)]

Farzam.at is a startup project for delivering services in various fields such as software development, mobile applications, web development, and IT consulting that I have collaborated on.

## -<u>Portfonext[Front-end Development(Next.js)]</u>

Portfonext is my personal **portfolio** project that showcases my abilities in **front-end development**, **UI design** and **up-to-date technologies**.

#### - <u>Bluetek</u> [Front-end Development(Vanilla)]

As a key contributor to the Bluetek project, I developed 5 unique landings and profiles that were both **visually appealing** and **user-friendly** and met the requirements of a **crypto-based** website.

# - <u>Modernist</u> [Front-end Development(Vanilla)]

Modernist is a personal project that showcases my expertise in designing a **Customizable HTML Template**.

# - Blue Wallet [UI/UX Design]

Blue Wallet is a crypto wallet UI/UX design in Adobe XD which is related to Bluetek project.

# - Park Speedy [UI/UX Design]

Park Speedy is a Figma project that showcases my **UI/UX design** skills for a startup app aimed at solving parking space issues.